You are seeing Ali ó
1 new girl sent a message
full of box
give you 1 colo there
so i'm wasting more time doing this
the problem is that i
that I'm operating at the wrong level of things
tell you the truth bro
the problems not so much in brownies
because the points of sale all the time so calling me
a brand gets really big
guy you have to put more people who have
experiences you don't have
that then we manage to accelerate the process
is on
Oh no
3 times
that's why I created this poster
I'm not actually looking for a loan shark
but find smart money
i need to find someone
who knows how to place my product
inside supermarket shelves
and has the expertise to negotiate with distributors
oh that's it bro eyes
so this is my proposal
if you have this requirement
you leave in the comments
maybe you can be our new partner in the company
tamo together
haha